# MUSKAN BHARGAVA

#### PRODUCT DESIGNER

Everything I've learned has been the culmination of nearly one year of work experience. Though I focus primarily on Product design, I'm equally passionate about front-end, branding, creative thinking, and product with a passion for delivering a great customer experience(UX).

#### +91 6377184775





shorturl.at/ewEIM

https://www.behance.net/muskanbhargava



# EXPERIENCE

#### UX designer

— August 2021-November 2021

Zilliqa Research

- Managed usability testing for Zilliqa landing pages in preparation for the website redesign.
- Defined testing parameters, prepared prototypes, recruited users, facilitated tests and reported results. Did the complete redesign of the Zilliqa website (28 pages)
- Focused on designing a scalable design solution that could work as a foundation for other content partners and a strategy for contextual navigation of content.

#### UX and UI Intern

— April 2021-May 2021

#### Zotalabs

- Designed an app and a website for a platform called ZedPrime.
- I was responsible for extracting functional requirements from end-users, customers, marketing, etc., and translating those requirements into detailed requirements by doing all the user research, ideating, designing, and user testing.
- Collaborated with graphic designers, web and app developers to translate information architecture, navigation and process flow into easy-to-use solutions.

#### UX Intern

— Jan 2021-March 2021

#### Olcademy

- Produced wireframes, design system, XHTML code and CSS that contributed to user-centred design (UCD) efforts for dozens of Web pages.
- 2 months in; I was given the responsibility of Product manager. My job was to assist and allocate BA and UX team members' tasks and ensure the timely completion of assignments.

# **EDUCATION**

#### BACHELOR'S

**—** 2018 - 2022

### The LNM Institute of Information Technology

- Member and Designer of Alumni Association (12 Posters and Certificates)
- Designer and member of Vivacity Graphics team (Cultural fest- Web Design and 15 Posters)
- Member and Designer of Media Cell (20+ posters)

#### HIGH SCHOOL (PCM)

**—** 2013 - 2017

#### Jayshree Periwal High School

Art Co-ordinator

# SKILLS & TOOLS

#### Tools

Figma, Adobe XD, Framer.Js, Illustrator, Photoshop, Miro, Sketch, Invision, Proto.io

#### Programming

HTML, CSS, React, C++,SQL,Python

# COURSES

#### Californian Institute of Arts

Visual Elements of User Interface Design Introduction to Typography

#### Google

Google UX Certificate